The #1 lever for
AI search
Ashley Christian  ·  Groundbreaker Marketing
But the reason
that we strongly
encourage our
clients to
publish all their
prices is due to
AI visibility
If you want to
show up in AI
search
the number one
lever that you
can pull for that
to happen is to
publish your
prices on your
website
If you do that
and your local
competitors are
not publishing
their prices on
their website
you are going to
be the most
commonly
referenced
company in that
AI search
like 100%
It's gonna be you
if you publish
your prices and
your competitors
aren't
So if you're
listening to
this
I hope you
publish your
prices on your
website or you
ask us to help
you with it
and hopefully
your surrounding
competitors don't
hear this advice
and do the same
thing
You wanna be the
first to do this
It really makes a
huge difference
in the AI
visibility